Guide to the School of Nursing, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1921-1979; Accession 19ND-A-410
  - Series XVI
    - Universities A -L, 1974-75 (Box 458, Folder 149)
    - Universities M -Z, 1974-75 (Box 458, Folder 150)
    - Reference Room Files
      - Abstracts, Series XVII (1975) Requests (Box 458, Folder 151)
      - Audio-Visual Indexing Tool Project, 1974-75 (Box 458, Folder 152)
      - Claims and Cancellations, 1975-1976 (Box 459, Folder 153)
      - Memos and Communication Miscellaneous with Medical Library, 1975 (Box 459, Folder 154)
      - Yale School of Nursing -Memos (Inter-School Administration), 1975 (Box 459, Folder 155)
      - Orders Recieved, 1974-75 (Box 459, Folder 156)
      - Orders Received, 1975-1976 (Box 459, Folder 157)
      - Reference Room Ledger, 1975-1976 (Box 459, Folder 158)
      - Suggestions for Purchase Yale School of Nursing and Yale Medical Library --Faculty Evaluations of Books, 1975 (Box 459, Folder 159)
    - Yale School of Nursing --Administration
      - Yale New Haven Hospital
        - Medical Clinic, 1974-75 (Box 459, Folder 161)
        - Miscellaneous, 1974-75 (Box 459, Folder 162)
        - Department of Psychiatry, 1974-75 (Box 459, Folder 163)
        - Primary Care Center, 1974-75 (Box 459, Folder 164)
        - Psychiatric Liaison, 1974-75 (Box 460, Folder 165)
      - Yale-New Haven Medical Center, Inc. (Dr. Pelligrino, Chairman), 1975 (Box 460, Folder 166-67)
      - Yale Women at Yale, 1974 (Box 460, Folder 168)
      - Yale University School of Nursing: (Joint Conference of School of Nursing Faculty and Yale-New Haven Hospital Department of Nursing, 1964-66 (Box 460, Folder 169)
    - Maternal-Newborn Department Files
      - Workshop: Cultural Implications of Childbearing, 1977 (Box 461, Folder 170-71)
      - Meridan-Wallingford Hospital, 1970-71 (Box 461, Folder 172)
      - Middletown- Dr. Magram, 1976-78 (Box 461, Folder 173)
      - Newborn Module, 1973 (Box 461, Folder 174)
      - City of New Haven, Department of Health - Dr. Brockway (Family Planning Clinics), 1971-1972 (Box 461, Folder 175)
      - Norwalk, 1971 (Box 461, Folder 176)
      - Norwalk Hospital, 1976 (Box 461, Folder 177)
      - Nurse-Midwifery Information - Services, 1973 (Box 461, Folder 178)
      - Parkside Evangeling Hotel (Pierce) and Housing, 1972-73 (Box 461, Folder 179)
      - Physical Diagnosis Unit, 1974 (Box 461, Folder 180)
      - Planned Parenthood Association (New Haven) - Mrs. Linda Gore (Box 461, Folder 181)
      - Pastpartium Module, 1975 (Box 461, Folder 182)
      - Postpartium Module, 1976 (Box 461, Folder 183)
      - Postpartium/Newborn/Contraception Module, 1975 (Box 461, Folder 184)
      - Prepared Childbirth and Parenthood Program, 1967-1972 (Box 461, Folder 185)
      - Program Directors Meeting, 1977 November 8-9 (Box 461, Folder 186)
      - Proposal or Position paper, 1973 January 26 (Box 461, Folder 187)
      - Statistics from Women's Clinic, 1969 October-May (Box 462, Folder 189)
    - Joint Administrative Committee, 1974-75 (Box 462, Folder 190)
    - Connecticut Regional Medical Program, 1974-75 (Box 462, Folder 191)
    - Connecticut State Board of Nursing Examiners, 1974-75 (Box 462, Folder 192)
    - Contemporary Practice Issues Seminar, 1974-75 (Box 462, Folder 193)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1974-75 (Box 462, Folder 194)
    - Dean's Office Miscellaneous Memos, 1974-75 (Box 462, Folder 195)
    - Department of Health,Education, and Welfare - Health and Resources Development, 1974-75 (Box 462, Folder 196)
    - Department of Health, Education and Welfare - Division of Nursing, 1974-75 (Box 462, Folder 197)
    - Evaluation - Three Year Program Master Program for College Graduates Group, 1975 (Box 462, Folder 198)
    - Executive Committee, 1974-75 (Box 462, Folder 199)
    - Faculty Publication, 1974-J5 (Box 462, Folder 200)
    - Faculty Research Interests, 1974-75 (Box 462, Folder 201)
    - Faculty and Staff Lists, 1974-75 (Box 462, Folder 202)
    - Annie W. Goodrich Professorship Visiting Professors, 1963-75 (Box 463, Folder 204)
    - Health Systems Agencies Executive, 1975-1976 (Box 463, Folder 205)
    - Health Systems Agencies, 1975-1976 (Box 463, Folder 206)
    - Hospice, Incorporated, 1974-75 (Box 463, Folder 207)
    - Hospice Board, 1974-75 (Box 463, Folder 208)
    - Committee on Research Involving Human Subjects, 1975-1976 (Box 463, Folder 209)
    - Inquiries - Faculty Positions, 1974-75 (Box 463, Folder 210)
    - Inquiries - Miscellaneous, 1974-75 (Box 463, Folder 211)
    - Issues Seminar, 1974-75 (Box 463, Folder 212)
    - Joint Administrative Committee, 1973-74 (Box 464, Folder 213)
    - Library, 1974-75 (Box 464, Folder 217)
    - Master Program for College Graduates
      - 3 Year Program Notes, 1975 (Box 464, Folder 218)
      - General, 1974-75 (Box 464, Folder 219)
      - Evaluation, 1974-75 (Box 464, Folder 220)
      - Minutes, 1974-75 (Box 464, Folder 221)
    - Master's Reports, 1974-75 (Box 464, Folder 222)
    - Medical Surgical Minutes, 1974-75 (Box 464, Folder 223)
    - New Haven Institute of Allied Health Careers, Incorporated, 1974-75 (Box 464, Folder 225)
    - New Haven Organizations, Miscellaneous, 1973-75 (Box 464, Folder 226)
    - Veterans Administration Hospital, 1974 (Box 465, Folder 227)
    - Veterans Administration Hospital: Deans Committee, 1973-74 (Box 465, Folder 228)
    - Veckerelli Prize, 1973-75 (Box 465, Folder 229)
    - Visiting Nurse Association -Regional, 1971-75 (Box 465, Folder 230)
    - Visitors to Yale School of Nursing, 1974-75 (Box 465, Folder 231)
    - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education (WICHE), 1974-75 (Box 465, Folder 232)
    - Yale School of Medicine Dean Berliner, 1974-75 (Box 465, Folder 233)
    - Yale School of Medicine Clinical Scholars Program, 1974-75 (Box 465, Folder 234)
    - Yale Comprehensive Cancer Center, 1974-75 (Box 465, Folder 235)
    - Yale -School of Medicine Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 465, Folder 236)
    - Yale School of Medicine Physician's Association Program, 1974 (Box 465, Folder 237)
    - Affirmative Action Proposal, 1973-75 (Box 465, Folder 238)
    - Alumni Fund, 1974-75 (Box 466, Folder 239)
    - Yale Alumni Fund, May, 1973-74 (Box 466, Folder 240)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, 1974 (Box 466, Folder 241)
    - Yale President Brewster, 1974-75 (Box 466, Folder 242)
    - Yale - Capital Campaign, 1973-74 (Box 466, Folder 243-244)
    - Yale - Comptroller, 1974-75 (Box 466, Folder 245)
    - Yale - Computer Center, 1974-75 (Box 466, Folder 246)
    - Yale Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, 1974 (Box 466, Folder 247)
    - Jonathan F. Fanton - Yale College, 1974-75 (Box 466, Folder 248)
    - Yale - Graduate Professional Student Senate, Incorporated, 1974-75 (Box 466, Folder 249)
    - Yale - Grant and Contract Administration, 1974-75 (Box 466, Folder 250)
    - Yale Housing, Parking, and Communications, 1974-75 (Box 466, Folder 251)
    - Yale - Health Maintenance Organizations Teaching Project, 1974 (Box 467, Folder 252)
    - Yale Deputy Provost G. Langdon, 1974 (Box 467, Folder 253)
    - Yale Medical Library, 1974-75 (Box 467, Folder 254)
    - Yale - Medical School Council, 1974 (Box 467, Folder 255)
    - Yale Miscellaneous, 1974-75 (Box 467, Folder 256)
    - Yale - News Bureau, 1968-75 (Box 467, Folder 257)
    - Yale - Oncology, General, 1974-75 (Box 467, Folder 258)
    - Yale - Office of University Developmaet, 1974-75 (Box 467, Folder 259)
    - Yale - Personnel Office, 1974-75 (Box 467, Folder 260)
    - Yale - Provost, 1974 (Box 467, Folder 261)
    - Yale - Secretary's Office, 1974 (Box 467, Folder 262)
    - Yale - University Health Plan, 1974-75 (Box 467, Folder 263)
    - University Health Board, 1974-75 (Box 467, Folder 264)
  - Series XVII
    - Financial Aid Office Records
      Restricted until January 1, 2051
      - Class of 1976 Financial Aid -Community Health MNN (Box 468, Folder 1)
      - Class of 1976 Financial Aid -Pediatrics, Psychiatry (Box 468, Folder 2)
      - Class of 1975 Financial Aid -Community Health, MNN (Box 468, Folder 3)
      - Class of 1975 Financial Aid -Pediatrics, Psychiatry (Box 468, Folder 4)
      - Class of 1974 Financial Aid -Community Health, MNN (Box 469, Folder 5)
      - Class of 1974 Financial Aid -Pediatrics, Psychiatry (Box 469, Folder 6)
      - Class of 1973 Second Year Financial Applications (Box 469, Folder 7)
      - Applications Received -Continuing Students, 1971-1972 (Box 469, Folder 8)
      - Applications received -New Students, 1971-1972 (Box 469, Folder 9)
      - Financial Aid Applications -Continuing Students, 1970-71 (Box 469, Folder 10)
      - Financial Aid Applications Received -Entering Students, 1970-71 (Box 470, Folder 11)
      - Finaincial Aid Applications, 1969-70 (Box 470, Folder 12)
      - University Loans, 1963-68 (Box 470, Folder 13)
      - HISMA-Project #942 -Pediatric Nurse Practitioner, 1972-73 (Box 470, Folder 14)
      - United States Public Health Service
        - Nursing Student Loan &Scholarship, 1973-74 (Box 470, Folder 15)
        - Nursing Student Loan and Scholarship, 1971-1972 (Box 470, Folder 16)
        - Nursing Student Lean and Scholarship, 1972-73 (Box 470, Folder 17)
        - Nursing Student Loan Program, 1970-71 (Box 470, Folder 18)
        - Nursing Student Scholarship, 1969-70 (Box 470, Folder 19)
        - Nursing Student Loan Program, 1968 (Box 470, Folder 20)
      - National Institute of Mental Health
        - 14 -2 TOl MH 07903, 1975-1976 (Box 470, Folder 21)
        - 13 -2 Tal MEl 07903, 1974-75 (Box 470, Folder 22)
        - 12 -2 T01 MH 07903, 1973-74 (Box 470, Folder 23)
        - 11 -2 T01 MH 07903, 1972-73 (Box 470, Folder 24)
        - 5 -10 -2 TOI ME 07903, 1971-1972 (Box 470, Folder 25)
        - 5 -Tl MH 07093-09, 1970-71 (Box 470, Folder 26)
        - 5 -T1 MH 07903-08, 1969-7a (Box 470, Folder 27)
        - 5 -T1 MH 07093-07, 1968-69 (Box 470, Folder 28)
      - Professional Nurse Traineeship 2 All
        - NU 00036-18, 1975-1976 (Box 470, Folder 29)
        - NU 00036-17, 1974-75 (Box 470, Folder 30)
        - NU 00036-16 S, 1973-74 (Box 470, Folder 31)
        - NU 00036-16, 1972-73 (Box 471, Folder 32)
        - NU 00036-15, 1971-1972 (Box 471, Folder 33)
        - NU,00036-14, 1970-71 (Box 471, Folder 34)
        - NU 00036-1381, 1969-70 (Box 471, Folder 35)
        - NU 00036-12, 1968-69 (Box 471, Folder 36)
    - Academy of Nursing, 1976-77 (Box 471, Folder 37)
    - Admissions Committee, 1976-77 (Box 471, Folder 38)
    - Advertising, 1976-1977 (Box 471, Folder 39)
    - Agreements -Clinical Experience, 1976 (Box 471, Folder 40)
    - Alumnae Association, 1976-77 (Box 471, Folder 41)
    - Yale School of Nursing tuumni College and Awards, 1976 (Box 471, Folder 42)
    - Alumnae Contributions, 1976-77 (Box 471, Folder 43)
    - Alumnae-Special-Capital Campaign, 1990-77 (Box 471, Folder 44)
    - Alumnae Steering Committee (Capital Campaign) (Box 471, Folder 45)
    - American Association of Colleges of Nursing, 1976-77 (Box 472, Folder 46)
    - American Nurses Association, 1976-77 (Box 472, Folder 47)
    - American Nurses Foundation, 1976-77 (Box 472, Folder 48)
    - American Nurses Association-Convention, 1976 (Box 472, Folder 49)
    - American Nurses Association Council of Nurse Researchers, 1976-77 (Box 472, Folder 50)
    - Yale School of Nursing Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 472, Folder 51)
    - Yale School of Nursing Annual Report, 1975 (Box 472, Folder 52)
    - Association of Community Health Service Agencies, Incorporated, 1975-1976 (Box 472, Folder 53)
    - Bellas Lecture, 1976-77 (Box 472, Folder 54)
    - Bixler Memorial, 1976 (Box 472, Folder 55)
    - Blue Cross, 1976 (Box 472, Folder 56)
    - Budget -Yale School of Nursing, 1976-77 (Box 472, Folder 58)
    - Clinical Arrangements for Masters Studies, 1976-77 (Box 472, Folder 59)
    - Commencement, 1976 (Box 472, Folder 60)
    - Community Health Care Plan, 1976-77 (Box 473, Folder 61-62)
    - Community Health Care Plan, 1975-1976 (Box 473, Folder 63)
    - Community Health, 1976-1977 (Box 473, Folder 64)
    - Community Health -General, 1975-75 (Box 473, Folder 65)
    - Community Health Course Materials, 1976-77 (Box 473, Folder 66-67)
    - Committee on Community Health Services, 1976-77 (Box 474, Folder 68)
    - Connecticut Mental Health Center, 1976-77 (Box 474, Folder 69)
    - Connecticut -miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 474, Folder 70)
    - Connecticut Nurse Practice Act, 1975 (Box 474, Folder 71)
    - Connecticut Public Health and Safety Committee, 1976-77 (Box 474, Folder 72)
    - Connecticut Regional Medical Program, 1975-1976 (Box 474, Folder 73)
    - Connecticut State Board of Nursing Examiners, 1975-1976 (Box 474, Folder 74)
    - Connecticut Student Nurses Association, 1975-1976 (Box 474, Folder 75)
    - Continuing Education Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 474, Folder 76)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 474, Folder 77)
    - Department of Hea!th, Education and Welfare -Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 474, Folder 78)
    - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, Div. of (Box 474, Folder 79)
    - Nursing, 1975-26 (Box 474, Folder system_indicator_36a21eb3632d897ce0295537e8c17c8d)
    - Dean's Office -Miscellaneous Memos, 1975-1977 (Box 474, Folder 80)
    - Executive Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 475, Folder 81-82)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1975-16 (Box 475, Folder 83)
    - Faculty Publications, 1974-76 (Box 475, Folder 84)
    - Family Practice -Yale Health Plan, 1975 (Box 475, Folder 86)
    - Health Systems Agency Governing Body, 1976 (Box 475, Folder 88)
    - New Haven Health Care -Health Systems Agency II Management Committee, 1976 (Box 475, Folder 89)
    - Health Systems Agency Search, 1976 (Box 475, Folder 90)
    - Insignia -3 year program, 1974-75 (Box 475, Folder 91)
    - Joint Appointments Task Force, 1975-1976 (Box 475, Folder 92)
    - Library, 1975-1977 (Box 476, Folder 96)
    - Long Range Planning Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 476, Folder 97)
    - Maternal-Newborn -General, 1975-1976 (Box 476, Folder 98)
    - Maternal -Newborn -General, 1975-1976 (Box 476, Folder 99)
    - Maternity Center, 1975-1976 (Box 476, Folder system_indicator_2dae3828c127cedeb7ab627a8e7ad2ca)
    - Medical/Surgical -General, 1975-1976 (Box 476, Folder 101)
    - Medical-Surgical Program Course Materials, 1975 (Box 476, Folder 102-03)
    - Medical-Surgical -General, 1975 (Box 476, Folder 104)
    - Miscellaneous, 1975-1977 (Box 476, Folder 105)
    - Move, 1976 (Box 476, Folder 106)
    - National Cancer Institute, 1975 (Box 477, Folder 107)
    - National League for Nursing Accreditation -Faculty Comments, 1976 (Box 477, Folder 108)
    - National League for Nursing -Miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 477, Folder 109)
    - National League for Nursing -Convention, 1975 May 18-21 (Box 477, Folder 110)
    - National League for Nursing -Council of Baccalaureate and Higher Degree Programs, 1975-1976 (Box 477, Folder 111)
    - New England Board of Higher Education (NEBHE -NECHEN), 1975-76 (Box 477, Folder 112)
    - NHHC Executive Committee, 1975 (Box 477, Folder 113-114)
    - Pediatrics -Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box 478, Folder 115)
    - Pediatrics -General, 1975-1976 (Box 478, Folder 116)
    - Pediatrics -General, 1975-1976 (Box 478, Folder 117)
    - Psychiatric -General, 1975-1976 (Box 478, Folder 118)
    - Yale School of Nursing Recruitment Committee, September 1974 -August 1976 (Box 478, Folder 119)
    - Recruitment -Community Health Nursing, 1975-1976 (Box 478, Folder 120)
    - Recruitment -Maternal Newborn, 1975-1976 (Box 478, Folder 121)
    - Recruitment -Medical/Surgical, 1975-1976 (Box 478, Folder 122)
    - Recruitment -miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 478, Folder 123)
    - Recruitment -(Psychiatric Nursing Program), 1975-1976 (Box 478, Folder 124)
    - Reference Room Records, 1975-1976 (Box 479, Folder 125-26)
    - Yale School of Nursing Renovation, 1975-1976 (Box 479, Folder 127)
    - Research Program, 1975-1977 (Box 479, Folder 128)
    - Student Affairs, 1975-1977 (Box 479, Folder 129)
    - Student Government, 1975-1977 (Box 479, Folder 130)
    - Three Year Program - Community Health Nursing, 1975-1976 (Box 479, Folder 131)
    - Three Year Program - Fundamentals of Clinical Science, 1975-1976 (Box 479, Folder 132)
    - Universities - miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 479, Folder 133)
    - Veterans Administration Dean's Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 480, Folder 134)
    - Veckerelli Price, 1975-1977 (Box 480, Folder 135)
    - Visitors to Yale School of Nursing, 1975-1977 (Box 480, Folder 136)
    - Writing Workshop, 1975-1976 (Box 480, Folder 138)
    - Medical School Dean Berliner, 1975-1976 (Box 480, Folder 139)
    - Yale School of Medicine Cancer Center, 1975-1976 (Box 480, Folder 140)
    - Yale School of Medicine - miscellaneous, 1975-1976 (Box 480, Folder 142)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, 1975-1977 (Box 480, Folder 143)
    - President Brewster, 1975-1977 (Box 480, Folder 144)
    - Affirmative Action, 1975-1977 (Box 480, Folder 145)
    - Capital Campaign, 1975-1976 (Box 480, Folder 146-147)
    - Child Study Center, 1975-1977 (Box 481, Folder 148)
    - Provost - H. Gray, 1975-1976 (Box 481, Folder 149)
    - Clinical Management for the Obstetrical Patient ISPS, 1975-1977 (Box 481, Folder 150)
    - Institute for Social and Policy Studies, 1975-1977 (Box 481, Folder 151)
    - G. Langdon - Deputy Provost, 1975-1977 (Box 481, Folder 152)
    - Medical Library, 1975-1976 (Box 481, Folder 153)
    - J. Mintz, Associate Provost, 1975-1977 (Box 482, Folder 154)
    - Yale - miscellaneous, 1975-1977 (Box 482, Folder 155)
    - Personnel, 1975-1977 (Box 482, Folder 156)
    - Secretaries Office, 1975-1976 (Box 482, Folder 157)
    - Treasurer's Office, 1974-76 (Box 482, Folder 158)
    - Health Services Center, 1975-1976 (Box 482, Folder 159)
    - Women at Yale, 1975-80 (Box 482, Folder 160)
    - Yale New Haven Hospital
      - Miscellaneous, 1975-1977 (Box 482, Folder 161)
      - Division of Nursing, 1975-1976 (Box 482, Folder 162)
      - Search Committee, 1975 (Box 482, Folder 163)
    - Yale New Haven Medical Center - Development Office, 1975-1977 (Box 482, Folder 165)
    - Alumnae Fund, 1975-1976 (Box 483, Folder 166)
    - Sigma Theta Tau, Study: P. Pierce: Analysis of Factors Describing Patients with End-stage Renal Failure, 1976 March 29 (Box 483, Folder 167)
    - Graduate Family Nurse Practitioner Training Grant - C. Januska, 1974-76 (Box 483, Folder 169)
    - D000028-02 c. Januska, Nov 1 1975 - Oct 31, 1976 (Box 483, Folder 170)
  - Series XVIII
    - Alumnae Bulletin, 1946-1949 (Box 484, Folder 1)
    - Associated Alumnae of Trained Nurses: second annual meeting, 1899 (Box 484, Folder 2)
    - Associated Alumnae of Trained Nurses: third annual convention, 1900 (Box 484, Folder 3)
    - Community Hospital News, 1945-46 (Box 484, Folder 4)
    - Ether Centenary, 1646-1946 (Box 484, Folder 5)
    - Goodrich, Annie W.: Alumnae Journal: Army School of Nursing, 1924-32 (Box 484, Folder 6)
    - Goodrich, Annie W.: Alumnae Journal: Army School of Nursing, 1933-37 (Box 484, Folder 7)
    - Leaders of American Nursing, 1924 (Box 484, Folder 8)
    - Medical Education in the United States and Canada, 1910 (Box 484, Folder 9)
    - Memorial presented by Dorothea L. Dix to the New Jersey Legislature urging New Jersey "to provide suitable asylum for the insane", 1845 (Box 484, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets, 1873-1943 (Box 485, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous: 25th Anniversary, 1949 (Box 485, Folder 12)
    - Nursing Guides: Arabic: Spanish, 1946 (Box 485, Folder 13)
    - Our-Hospital, 1939-42 (Box 486, Folder 14)
    - Publicity posters, undated (Box 486, Folder 15)
    - Watch Tower, 1941-42 (Box 486, Folder 16)
    - King Edward's Hospital Fund for London: Pensions for Hospital Officers and Staffs, 1919 (Box 486, Folder 17)
    - Graphs and charts (Box 288)
    - Pages from sweet-sixteen "comic book on Yale" Student Nurse write-up, 1947-1949 (Box 1A)
    - Teaching Tapes: interview with Maternity patient, 1951 (Box 2A)
- Records, circa 1921-1979; Accession 1982-A-060
  - Advisors - Master's Reports, 1976-77 (Box 487, Folder 1)
  - Clinical Experlence Agreements, 1976-77 (Box 487, Folder 2)
  - Clinical Experience Agreements, 1977 (Box 487, Folder 3)
  - Alumnae College Awards, 1977 (Box 487, Folder 4)
  - Alumnae Contributions - Bixler Memorial Fund, 1977 (Box 487, Folder 5)
    Restricted until January 1, 2052
  - Annual Report - Five Year, 1976-77 (Box 487, Folder 6)
  - Brown Shoe Scholarship, 1977 (Box 487, Folder 7)
  - Building Moves - Yale School of Nursing, Key Code, 1976 (Box 487, Folder 8)
  - Building Dedication, 1977 (Box 487, Folder 9)
  - Commencement, 1977 (Box 487, Folder 10)
  - Government Relations Council - CAN, 1976-77 (Box 487, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut State Board of Nurse Examiners, 1976-77 (Box 488, Folder 12)
  - Continuing Education, 1976-77 (Box 488, Folder 13)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1976-77 (Box 488, Folder 14)
  - Curriculum Charts, 1976 (Box 488, Folder 15)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare - miscellaneous, 1976-77 (Box 488, Folder 16)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare-- Division of Nursing, 1976-77 (Box 488, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee, 1976-77 (Box 488, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Publications, 1976-77 (Box 488, Folder 19)
  - Financial Aid Applications and Records, Class of 1977
    - Second Year of Specialization, A-J, 1976-77 (Box 488, Folder 20)
    - Second Year of Specialization, K-0, 1976-77 (Box 489, Folder 21)
    - Second Year of Specialization, P-W, 1976-77 (Box 489, Folder 22)
  - Health Services Association Executive Committee, 1976-77 (Box 489, Folder 23)
  - Health Servtces Association Governing Body, 1976-77 (Box 489, Folder 24)
  - Hospice Board, 1976-77 (Box 489, Folder 25)
  - Inquiries - Faculty Positions, 1976-77 (Box 490, Folder 26)
  - Inquiries - Miscellaneous, 1976-77 (Box 490, Folder 27)
  - Issues (N-501) - Course Materials, 1976-77 (Box 490, Folder 28)
  - Malpractice Insurance, 1976-77 (Box 490, Folder 31)
  - Maternal-Newborn, 1976-77 (Box 490, Folder 32)
  - Medical Regional Activities and Continuing Education, 1975-76 (Box 490, Folder 34)
  - Medical/Surgical (Nursing), 1976-77 (Box 490, Folder 35)
  - Medical/Surgical Course Materials, 1976-77 (Box 491, Folder 36-37)
  - National League for Nursing, 1976-77 (Box 491, Folder 38)
  - New England Council for Higher Education in Nursing (NECHE), 1976-77 (Box 491, Folder 39)
  - New Haven Health Care, 1976-77 (Box 491, Folder 40)
  - Occupational Health, 1976-77 (Box 491, Folder 42-43)
  - Pediatrics, 1976-77 (Box 492, Folder 44)
  - Pediatrics Course Materials, I, 1976-77 (Box 492, Folder 45)
  - Pediatrics Course Materials, II, 1976-77 (Box 492, Folder 46)
  - Primary Nursing, 1936-77 (Box 492, Folder 47)
  - Psychiatry, 1976-77 (Box 492, Folder 48)
  - Psychiatry Course Materials, 1976-77 (Box 492, Folder 49-50)
  - Recruitment Committee, 1976-77 (Box 492, Folder 51)
  - Recruitment - Affirmative Action, 1976-79 (Box 493, Folder 52)
  - Recruitment - Community Health, 1976-79 (Box 493, Folder 53)
  - Recruitment-- Psychiatric Chairperson Search, 1977 (Box 493, Folder 54)
  - Recruitment - Psychiatric CMHC Director Search, 1977 (Box 493, Folder 55)
  - Recruitment - Psychiatry, 1976-77 (Box 493, Folder 56)
  - Recruitment - CMHC Clinical Specialist / Faculty, 1976-77 (Box 493, Folder 57)
  - Recruitment - Mailing Lists; Associate Director of Nursing; Clinical Specialists, 1976-77 (Box 493, Folder 58)
  - Recruitment - Research, 1976-77 (Box 493, Folder 59)
  - Reference Room - I, 1977-78 (Box 493, Folder 60)
  - Reference Room - II, 1977-78 (Box 493, Folder 61)
  - Reference Room - III, 1977-78 (Box 493, Folder 62)